The Guide to the Jerome Charyn Papers 1937-1997 MSS.044
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Subseries A: General (1955-1997)
    - Sirat, Rene Samuel, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Smid, Jan, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Smith, Martin J., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Smith, Verna, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Societe Nationale de Television France 3, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Sondheim, Stephen, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Soulat, Robert, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Sovaj, Natacha (Sixieme Continent), undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Spatz, Ronald, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Sphere Books Limited, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Staletti, Luca Aurelio, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Stark, Sharon, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Stade, George, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Stadtkino, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Stanford Unifersitiy, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Stavridis, Yves, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Stefanova, Lilyana (Literaturen Front), undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Stein, Abner, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Stephens, Christopher P., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Stern, Daniel, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Stubin, E., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Suhewich, Ron, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - The School of Visual Arts, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Sweeting, Joseph G., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Sypniewski, Frances A., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Tabachnick, Maud, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 28 (T))
    - Taibo, Paco Ignacio, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 28 (T))
    - Tausig, Otto, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 28 (T))
    - Thalia Productions, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 28 (T))
    - Thomas, Brook, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 28 (T))
    - Thompson, Jack, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 28 (T))
    - Topin, Tito, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 28 (T))
    - Torberg, Peter, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 28 (T))
    - Torrey, Kate, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 28 (T))
    - The TransAtlantic Review, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 28 (T))
    - TriQuarterly, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 28 (T))
    - United States Information Agency Reception Center, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 29 (U-V))
    - The University of North Carolina at Charlotte, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 29 (U-V))
    - University Press of Mississippi, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 29 (U-V))
    - Uniwersytet Warszawski (Warsaw University), undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 29 (U-V))
    - Updike, John, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 29 (U-V))
    - Vachss, Andrew Henry, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 29 (U-V))
    - Vaillant, Gerard, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 29 (U-V))
    - Victor, Ed, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 29 (U-V))
    - Vieillescares, Pierre, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 29 (U-V))
    - The Virginia Quarterly Review, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 29 (U-V))
    - Viselthier, Bernard and Annie, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 29 (U-V))
    - Vogel, Afton, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 29 (U-V))
    - Voyce, Ed, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 29 (U-V))
    - W., Catherine, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Wade, James O., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Wagner, W. Jane, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Waldhorn, Arthur, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Walker, Aaron, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Walsh, Drusilla, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Walter, LuAnn, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Walzer, Wendy, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Watanabe, Masakiyo, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Weingarten, J., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Weiss, Jan, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Weiss, Nicki, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Weissman, Rosalind, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Wellington, Fred, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Wesleyan University, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 15 (W-Z))
    - Weston, B., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 15 (W-Z))
    - Wetzstein, Ross, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Wexler, Sylvia, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Whitlow, Hubert, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Whittle, Anita, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Who's Who in America, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Wilen, Lydia, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Willis, Michael, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Wilson, Carter, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Winnick, Louis, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Winterport, Philip, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Wittenberg, Polly, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Wittmann, Wolfgang, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Wolfe, Ira, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Wolfberg, Dorothy, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Wallis E. Wood, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Writers Guild of America, East, Inc., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
    - Zomba Books, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 30 (W-Z))
  - Subseries B: Prominent Individual Correspondents
    - Anissimov, Myriam, 1980-1989; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Arbor House, 1975-1983; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Avon Books, 1966-1981; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Bay, Marie-Pierre, 1988-1996; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Bloc-Rodot, Cecile, 1990-1997; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Borchardt, Georges and Georges Borchardt, Inc, 1980-1988; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Century, Douglas, 1985-1997; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Charyn, Fannie and Sam Parents), 1967-1986; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Cheetam, Mic Anthony Sheil Associates), 1984-1989; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Chenetier, Marc, 1983-1992; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Cohen, Hy, 1975-1981; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Cohen-Solal, Annie, 1982-1989; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - College Caniviez Students), 1993; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - College Paul Valery Students), 1997; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - De Kerret, Hughes, 1984-1989; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - De Loustal, J., 1987-1990; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Donadio, Candida, 1964-1967; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Donadio, Candida, 1968-1976; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Ferri, Sandro, 1986-1988; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Fine, Donald, 1984-1988; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Flomenhaft-Flomine, Deborah, 1974-1984; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Frisch, Marianne, 1974-1990; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Fuller, Christa and Samuel, 1989-1997; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Gallois, Claire, 1982-1984; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Gold, Herbert, 1968-1991; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Guerard, Albert, 1976-1993; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Harper & Row, 1962-1978; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Harrington, Lynne, 1985-1986; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Harrison, Chantal, 1987-1990; 31142040612338 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Karapanou, Margarita, 1979-1993; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Keeley, Edmund, 1979-1993; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Lapautre, Michelle, 1974-1980; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Lapautre, Michelle Agency), 1981-1995; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Lehman College, 1968-1979; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Liepman AG Eva Koralnik), 1980-1989; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Lish, Gordon, 1974-1983; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Co., 1963-1970; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Neugebogen, Jay, 1967-1997; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Patten, Robert, 1979-1989; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Patten, Robert, 1990-1997; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Pelikan-Straus, Nina, 1978-1986; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Philips-Charyn-Lily, Marlene, 1964-1988; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Purdy, James, 1981-1984; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Random House, 1964-1986; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Shoenfeld, Rivka, 1977-1981; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Sipper, Ralph, 1983-1986; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Tuten, Frederick, 1975-1984; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - The Viking Press, Inc., 1963-1970; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Voice Project, 1967; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Woolf, Mike, 1976-1989; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Subseries C: Outgoing correspondence
    - Outgoing correspondence, 1963-1998; 31142040612346 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Series II: Accounting
  - Tax Documents, 1964-1965; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Tax Documents, 1966-1969; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Tax Documents, 1969; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Bank Account Books, Receipts, 1970-1980; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Copies of Tax Returns, 1970; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Tax Documents, 1970; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Bank Statements, 1971; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Copies of Tax Returns, 1971; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Expenses, 1971; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Tax Documents, 1971; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Bank Statements, 1972; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Tax Documents, 1972; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Check Stubs, 1973; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Copies of Tax Returns, 1973; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Entertainment and Food Receipts, 1973; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Leases, 1973-1977; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Tax Documents, 1973; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Travel Expenses, 1973; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Check Stubs, 1974; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Copies of Tax Returns, 1974; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Entertainment and Food Receipts, 1974; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Tax Documents, 1974; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Travel Expenses, 1974; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Check Stubs and Receipts, 1975; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Copies of Tax Returns, 1975; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Tax Documents, 1975; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Check Stubs and Receipts, 1976; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Copies of Tax Returns, 1976; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Tax Documents, 1976; 31142040612353 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Bank Statements, 1977; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Business Expenses, 1977; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Copies of Tax Returns, 1977; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Dividends, 1977; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Tax Documents, 1977; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Travel Expenses, 1977; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Writing Expenses, 1977; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Bank Savings Accounts Documents, 1978-1980; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Bank Statements, Receipts, 1978; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Check Stubs, 1978; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Entertainment Expenses, 1978; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Tax Documents, 1978; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Copies of Tax Returns, 1979; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Entertainment Expenses, 1979; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Health, 1979-1980; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Tax Documents - 1 of 2, 1979; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Tax Documents - 2 of 2, 1979; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Business Expenses, 1980; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Entertainment Expenses, 1980; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Utilities, 1980; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Tax Documents, 1980, 1980; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - University of Texas, Austin reciepts, 1980; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Series III: Education and Employment
  1942-1996
  - Application for Air Force Academy Oct., 1959; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Application for Teaching Position, Hunter College Jun, 1961; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Colloquium papers for Professors Chiappe and Oswald, undated; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Columbia College Examinations and Essays, 1955-1959; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Curriculum Vitae, 1964-1977; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - English Papers - 1 of 2, undated; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - English Papers for Professor Nobbe, undated; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Fiction Project for Professor Sugarman, undated; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Film Course Student Evaluations, 1996; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Humanities, Education, Russian - Papers, undated; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - ID's, documents and notes., undated; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Public School # 61 / Herman Ridder Junior High, 1942-1951; 31142040612379 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Series IV: Notebooks, Notes and Source Materials
  - Untitled notebooks - 1 of 2, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Untitled notebooks - 2 of 2, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - The Ambassadors, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - American Scrapbook, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - American Scrapbook - Enclosures, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Batman Comic Book (1990) / Back to Batman / Aborted Novel (1991-1992), 1990-1992; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Batman Comic Book / Maria's Girls, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Blue Eyes source materials, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - The Catfish Man - notebooks 1-4, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - The Catfish Man - notebooks 1-4 - Enclosures, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - The Catfish Man - notebook 5 / Darlin' Bill, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - The Catfish Man Source Materials, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - A Child's History of the Bronx, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - A Child's History of the Bronx - Mandrake, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - A Child's History of the Bronx - Public School for the Performing Arts Essay and Notes, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - The Dark Lady from Belorusse / Interview with Francis Ford Coppola, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Darlin' Bill - notebook 1, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Darlin' Bill - notebooks 2-4, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Darlin' Bill notes, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Eisenhower, My Eisenhower / A Child's History of the Bronx, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Eisenhower, My Eisenhower - Enclosure, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Elsinore / King George notes, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Elsinore / Good Policeman, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Family Man, Book 2, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - The Franklin Scare, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Frog Man (Paradise Man) / Billy Budd / Margot / King George, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Frog Man (Paradise Man) - notebook 2, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Jewish Tradition, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - King George (play) / Movieland / Brides (screenplay) / Boys of Sheriff Book (comic book), undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - King Jude / The Catfish Man, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - King Jude, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - King Jude - Enclosures, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - King Jude - History of Hungary by Denis Sinor (photocopy of Chapter 7), undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - King Jude source materials, undated; 31142040612387 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Lehman College, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Lehman College - Enclosures, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Little Angel Street, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Little Angel Street / Scenario for Graphic Novel, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Marilyn the Wild, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Marilyn Screenplay / At War With the Wolfman / Maria's Girls, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Middle English, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Metropolis / Frog Man (Paradise Man), undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Movieland / King George / Metropolis, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Navy, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Panna Maria, notebooks 1-2, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Panna Maria, notebooks 3-7, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Panna Maria - New Beginning and End, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Panna Maria - Elis Island booklet, newspaper articles and notes., undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Paradise Man Screenplay / Young Isaac / Back to Batman / New Ending to Elsinore, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Patrick Silver, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Pinocchio, notebooks 1-2, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Pinocchio, notebooks 3-4, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Pinocchio, notebook 5, notes, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Secret Isaac, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - The Seventh Babe - notebooks 1-4, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - The Seventh Babe - notebooks 5-7, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - The Tar Baby, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Werewolf, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Werewolf - Enclosure, undated; 31142040612395 (Box 8, Folder 59)
- Series V: Date Books
  - Address and Telephone Book - 1 of 2, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Address and Telephone Book - 2 of 2, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1969; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1970; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1971; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1973; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Appointment Calendar - Enclosures, 1973; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1974; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Appointment Calendar - Enclosures, 1974; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1975; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Appointment Calendar - Enclosures, 1975; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1976; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Appointment Calendar - Enclosures, 1976; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1977; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Appointment Calendar - Enclosures, 1977; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1978; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Appointment Calendar - Enclosures, 1978; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1979; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Appointment Calendar - Enclosures, 1979; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Appointment Calendar, 1980; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Appointment Calendar - Enclosures, 1980; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Series VI: Photographs
  - Atkins, Linda Keep - 2 photos, 1995; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Bobst Library Reading - 3 photos, 1995; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - The Catfish Man, by James Aronovsky - 1 photo, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Charyn, Jerome and Marlene - 8 photos, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Charyn, Herbert Gold and Barnet Rossell, by Mariana Cook, 1986; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Charyn - various photographs, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Contact Sheets from Zomba Group, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Cover Design - Tar Baby - 8 photos + enclosures, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Cover Design - Interno Giallo - 1 phots, 1989; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Ferri's daughter - 1 photo, 1989; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Frezzato, Mazzimiliano - 1 photo, 1992; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Gilliard, Claire - 1 photo, 1982; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Hickins, Michael - 1 photo, 1989; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Katz, Laura - 1 photo, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Lehman, William - 3 polaroids, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Lily Charyn), Marlene - 1 photo + enclosure, 1988; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Moustaki, Vladimir - 1 photo, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Nabatoff, Dawn - 1 photo, 1981; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Negatives, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - New York - 7 photos + enclosures, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - New York Portfolio - 16 photos, 1990; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Panna Maria - Ellis Island - 5 photos, 1980; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Photos taken at Breadloaf - 3 photos + enclosure, 1983; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Photos Received From Marc Chenetier, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Photos Received From Editiones Jucar-2 photos, 1987; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Photos Received From Elle, 1990; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Photos Received From James Fellows - 1 slide, 1986; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Photos Received From Margarita Karapanou the Island of Hydra) 2 photos, 1982; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Photos Received From Hugh Mo - 3 photos, 1986; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Photos Received From Jay Neubogen - 3 photos, 1996; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Photos Received From Rivka Shoenfeld - 2 photos, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Photos Received From W. J. Wagner - 7 photos, 1983; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Portraits - 1 of 3 - 5 photos, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Portraits - 2 of 3 - 3 photos, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Portraits - 3 of 3 - 1 photo, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Portraits - by Jerry Bauer - 1 photo, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Portraits - by Marlene Charyn - 1 photo, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Portraits - by T. Ligameri - 10 photos, 1978; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 38)